{
    "subject": "resource/Barcelona\u2013Cerb\u00e8re_railway",
    "predicate": "ontology/location",
    "object": "resource/Catalonia",
    "human_readable": "The location of the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway is in Catalonia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9579538106918335,
            "question": "Where is the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9175540208816528,
            "question": "Can you describe the region where the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway is situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9119381308555603,
            "question": "What is the name of the region where the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway is situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8941517472267151,
            "question": "Is the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway located within a specific country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8057711124420166,
            "question": "Which region in Spain is home to the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7833294868469238,
            "question": "Are there other notable features or landmarks near the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7096291780471802,
            "question": "What geographical area does the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway traverse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6796718239784241,
            "question": "How might the location of the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway influence its usage or importance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5823582410812378,
            "question": "What type of transportation infrastructure is the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4991879463195801,
            "question": "Could you explain the historical significance of the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The location of the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway is in Catalonia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2885_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of transportation infrastructure is the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2885_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might the location of the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway influence its usage or importance?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2885_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What geographical area does the Barcelona-Cerb\u00e8re railway traverse?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2885_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2885_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2885_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2885_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2885_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2885_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2885_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2885_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2885_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2885_83.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2885_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that the Barcelona\u2013Cerb\u00e8re railway passes through the Catalan regional cities of Girona and Figueres, which suggests that it also exists within Catalonia."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents support that the Barcelona\u2013Cerb\u00e8re railway passes through Catalonia, Spain, as evidenced by statements like \"linking Barcelona in Catalonia, Spain to Cerb\u00e8re in France\" and mentioning stations like Granollers Centre which is also in Catalonia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}